Full Stack Developer

Entry Level



Stefanos Dimitriou

myLinkedIn

myGithub

stefanosdim@gmail.com

+30 6942 624 626

Athens, Greece



in

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python, C++
- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- MySQL
- Django
- React JS
- Angular
- Bootstrap
- Git

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Communication / Negotiation
- Work Ethic
- Problem-Solving
- Flexibility /Adaptability
- Mathematical Thinking

LANGUAGES

- Greek (Native)
- English (Fluent)

INTERESTS

- Chess
- Drawing
- Books
- Movies /Series
- DnD

ABOUT ME

After a long career in the automations and manufacturing industry as a production operator and technician I decided to pivot careers into programming as a full-stack software developer.

The combination of my technical and quantitative background along with my communication skills, developed through education and work experience over the past years, I believe would make me a great-fit in your company in today's environment.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Software Developer, Python Stream PeopleCert, 6-month Coding Bootcamp, online

2021 - 2022

2019 - today

Computer Science

Elliniko Anoixto Panepistimio, Patra GR.

Modules: C++, advanced mathematics, algorithms, mathematical logic,

discrete mathematics, SQLite, digital systems

Administrative and Economical Business Executive 2001 - 2003

Vocational Training Institute, Markopoulo Athens GR.

Economic, financial, organization & administration direction 1999 General Certificate of Secondary Education, Athens GR.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Production Operator & Technician

2010 - today

Theodorou Automations SAICT, Paiania Athens GR.

- Produce, Inspect and test products successfully for over 10 years.
- Trained 5 people.
- Supervise 2 workers in regards to the manufacturing line in the production of the goods in the company.
- Organize and improve production data base.

Business Development Associate

2004 - 2010

Study Tours, Marousi Athens GR

- Assisted in a significant increase in the overall inbound amount of student groups.
- Closing agreements with many universities and corresponding agents in the UK in regards to the requirements for admitting students into their cohorts.
- Trained 4 people.
- Being Group Leader and Tourist Guide for many foreign student groups.
- Administrator of the company's data base.

CERTIFICATES

- PeopleCert Software Developer Foundation and Advanced, online
- Eventora WordPress free seminar, online
- Stafford House English Language Certification, Canterbury Kent UK.

LEADERSHIP

- Took the initiative to create a discord server in order to connect all the students of the university studying computer science which now has over 1,000 active members.
- Being a moderator in various forums, chat rooms and gaming sites